[Music]
a lot of food I feel for funny things
that I food a key primary school tests
for two times and I filled three times
for the middle school middle schools you
know for three years I tried fill in the
universities so I applied jobs or 30
times got rejected
I went for a police if you know you're
not good I went to you know even the KFC
when KFC came to check on drive a
university 24 people went for the job 23
people accepted I was the only a guy and
we went for please five people all of
them accepted I was the only guy deny
respectful people so to me being turned
down rejected oh by the way I told you
that I was I apply for Harvard for ten
times rejected I know if you reject all
right now I think we have to get used to
it we're not that good even today we
still have a lot of people reject us I
don't think in this world a lot of
people be rejected more than thirty
times if we you know the only thing we
never give up the only thing like we
like a forest to God we keep on fight we
give on change ourselves we don't
complain whether you are successful not
successful I find a one people when they
finish the job if they make the mistake
of the film if they always completely
others this guy will never come back if
the guy only check himself yeah
something wrong with me here something
one meter there this guy has a hope
[Music]
you